<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Find Local Farms Near You! on Farms Finder</title>
    <link>https://farmfinders.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Find Local Farms Near You! on Farms Finder</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://farmfinders.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://farmfinders.ca/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://farmfinders.ca/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last updated: January 1, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Farm Finder Canada. We are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring the security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website and use our services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-we-collect&#34;&gt;Information We Collect&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-you-provide-directly&#34;&gt;Information You Provide Directly&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;: When you contact us through forms or email, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, and message content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Preferences&lt;/strong&gt;: When you search for farms, we may store your location preferences to improve your experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-collected-automatically&#34;&gt;Information Collected Automatically&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usage Data&lt;/strong&gt;: We collect information about how you interact with our website, including pages visited, time spent, and search queries.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Device Information&lt;/strong&gt;: We may collect information about your device, including IP address, browser type, operating system, and device identifiers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Data&lt;/strong&gt;: With your consent, we may collect approximate location data to help you find nearby farms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cookies-and-similar-technologies&#34;&gt;Cookies and Similar Technologies&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Farm Finder Canada</title>
      <link>https://farmfinders.ca/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://farmfinders.ca/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-farm-finder-canada&#34;&gt;About Farm Finder Canada&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-we-solve&#34;&gt;The Problem We Solve&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finding reliable, up-to-date information about local farms shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a challenge. Too often, families searching for farm experiences encounter outdated websites, disconnected phone numbers, or fragmented information scattered across multiple platforms. We created Farm Finder Canada to bridge this gap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We connect people directly with farmers across Canada, providing a single, reliable source for current farm information. Our goal is to make it easy for families to discover authentic farm experiences while helping farmers reach the customers they serve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://farmfinders.ca/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://farmfinders.ca/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get In Touch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re here to help connect you with the best farm experiences across Canada. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a visitor looking for the perfect farm or a farmer wanting to reach more customers, we&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@farmsfinders.ca&#34;&gt;hello@farmsfinder.ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We typically respond within 24 hours during business days.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;frequently-asked-questions&#34;&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;for-farm-visitors&#34;&gt;For Farm Visitors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-find-farms-near-me&#34;&gt;How do I find farms near me?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use our farm finder tool on the homepage. Simply select your farm type (Christmas trees, pumpkin patches, etc.), choose your province, and then your city to see available farms in your area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Briggs Trees</title>
      <link>https://farmfinders.ca/farms/briggs-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://farmfinders.ca/farms/briggs-trees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Briggs Trees is a family-owned and operated Christmas tree farm that has been serving the Ottawa area for 35 years. Spanning 100 acres of woods, the farm offers a variety of tree species including spruce, balsam, and Scotch pine for customers to cut their own. Visitors can enjoy a peaceful walk through the scenic property and select the perfect natural tree for their holiday celebrations. In addition to the cut-your-own experience, the farm also provides natural Christmas wreaths for purchase. With its long history and commitment to providing a high-quality, authentic Christmas tree experience, Briggs Trees is a beloved destination for families in the region.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
