<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Find Local Farms Near You! on Farms Finder</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Find Local Farms Near You! on Farms Finder</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-ca</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/privacy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;privacy-policy&#34;&gt;Privacy Policy&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Last updated: January 1, 2024&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Farm Finder Canada. We are committed to protecting your privacy and ensuring the security of your personal information. This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and safeguard your information when you visit our website and use our services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;information-we-collect&#34;&gt;Information We Collect&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-you-provide-directly&#34;&gt;Information You Provide Directly&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Contact Information&lt;/strong&gt;: When you contact us through forms or email, we may collect your name, email address, phone number, and message content.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Preferences&lt;/strong&gt;: When you search for farms, we may store your location preferences to improve your experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;information-collected-automatically&#34;&gt;Information Collected Automatically&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Usage Data&lt;/strong&gt;: We collect information about how you interact with our website, including pages visited, time spent, and search queries.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Device Information&lt;/strong&gt;: We may collect information about your device, including IP address, browser type, operating system, and device identifiers.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Data&lt;/strong&gt;: With your consent, we may collect approximate location data to help you find nearby farms.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;cookies-and-similar-technologies&#34;&gt;Cookies and Similar Technologies&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Farm Finder Canada</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;about-farm-finder-canada&#34;&gt;About Farm Finder Canada&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-problem-we-solve&#34;&gt;The Problem We Solve&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Finding reliable, up-to-date information about local farms shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a challenge. Too often, families searching for farm experiences encounter outdated websites, disconnected phone numbers, or fragmented information scattered across multiple platforms. We created Farm Finder Canada to bridge this gap.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;our-mission&#34;&gt;Our Mission&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We connect people directly with farmers across Canada, providing a single, reliable source for current farm information. Our goal is to make it easy for families to discover authentic farm experiences while helping farmers reach the customers they serve.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;contact-us&#34;&gt;Contact Us&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;get-in-touch&#34;&gt;Get In Touch&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re here to help connect you with the best farm experiences across Canada. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a visitor looking for the perfect farm or a farmer wanting to reach more customers, we&amp;rsquo;d love to hear from you.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Email&lt;/strong&gt;: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@farmsfinders.ca&#34;&gt;hello@farmsfinder.ca&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We typically respond within 24 hours during business days.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;frequently-asked-questions&#34;&gt;Frequently Asked Questions&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;for-farm-visitors&#34;&gt;For Farm Visitors&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;how-do-i-find-farms-near-me&#34;&gt;How do I find farms near me?&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Use our farm finder tool on the homepage. Simply select your farm type (Christmas trees, pumpkin patches, etc.), choose your province, and then your city to see available farms in your area.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Aldor Acres Christmas Trees</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/aldor-acres-christmas-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/aldor-acres-christmas-trees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Al-Dor Farms is a family-run farm in Glen Valley, just 5 km east of historic Fort Langley. Albert and Dorothy Anderson bought the land in 1971, and by 1988, they had placed a small sign and an honour-system jar at the end of the road to sell pumpkins. What began as a simple roadside idea quickly grew into a beloved local tradition, complete with tractor-drawn hayrides and hands-on farm experiences.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Alouette Tree Farm Ltd</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/alouette-tree-farm-ltd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/alouette-tree-farm-ltd/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Alouette Christmas Tree Farm is a family-owned and operated farm located in the beautiful community of Maple Ridge, BC. With a strong commitment to tradition and quality, the farm provides families with fresh Christmas trees and handcrafted wreaths, bringing the warmth and magic of the season from their farm to your home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Known for their Grand Firs, Noble Firs, and Fraser Firs, the team at Alouette takes great pride in ensuring that each tree is healthy, full, and ready to be decorated. Customers appreciate the farm’s welcoming atmosphere, knowledgeable staff, and the care they put into helping families select the perfect holiday centerpiece.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bachner Family Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/bachner-family-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/bachner-family-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bachner Family Christmas Tree Farm is rooted in a proud family tradition that began over 40 years ago, when Michael Bachner Sr. planted the farm’s very first Christmas trees. Today, four generations later, the Bachner family continues to carry on that legacy, nurturing trees with the same dedication and care that started it all.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The farm is committed to sustainable growth and hands-on care. Each tree is hand-trimmed in early summer, and with the help of irrigation, fertilization, and careful maintenance, the Bachners ensure that every tree grows healthy, full, and ready for families to enjoy. In April 2025, the farm introduced a new planting of Balsam–Fraser Fir cross trees, which will take several years to mature and offer even more variety for future generations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Balsam Ridge Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/balsam-ridge-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/balsam-ridge-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Balsam Ridge Christmas Tree Farm in Burtts Corner, New Brunswick, is a welcoming family-run destination for fresh, beautifully shaped Christmas trees. Known for their friendly service and family-friendly atmosphere, the owners go out of their way to make the experience enjoyable—especially for kids.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The farm offers a choose-and-cut experience, where visitors can walk the grounds and tag their perfect tree for the season. Customers often praise the trees for being full, healthy, and well-shaped, ensuring every family can bring home a tree that’s just right for their holiday celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Barrett&#39;s Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/barretts-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/barretts-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Barrett’s Christmas Tree Farm opens for the season on November 29, 2025, welcoming families daily from 9am to 5pm through Christmas Eve. A family-owned farm rooted in tradition, Barrett’s offers both U-Cut and Pre-Cut Christmas trees, including premium Blue Spruce, with trees available in a variety of sizes. U-Cut trees up to 8ft are $62, with limited options above 8ft, while Pre-Cut trees range from $60–$110.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The farm is more than a place to find your perfect tree—it’s a holiday destination. Guests can enjoy the Family Fun Farm area (booking recommended), cozy up with hot chocolate or hot apple cider at the new Snack Shack, and indulge in treats like Grandma’s shortbread cookies, butter crunch chocolate, popcorn, and s’mores kits. On weekends, wagon rides run throughout the day, while horse-drawn wagon and sleigh rides add a magical touch for just $5 (weather permitting).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bastien Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/bastien-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/bastien-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Bastien Christmas Tree Farm has been family-owned and operated since 1995, proudly helping families create lasting holiday traditions. With approximately 15,000 trees at various stages of growth, including firs, spruces, and pines, the farm offers a wide selection of beautiful fresh trees for every home.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;More than just a tree farm, Bastien Christmas Tree Farm is a destination for festive family outings. Guests can enjoy the nature trail, cozy campfire, photo centre, concession stand, and more, making each visit a memorable holiday experience.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>BellyAcres Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/bellyacres-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/bellyacres-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;BellyAcres Tree Farm is a family-friendly destination where holiday traditions come alive. Conveniently located just off the main road, the farm makes it easy for families to choose and cut their own Christmas tree. Visitors often remark on the welcoming atmosphere, friendly staff, and the care Andrew and Louise take to ensure everyone has a memorable experience.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The farm offers a wide selection of well-trimmed pines and firs at reasonable prices, along with thoughtful touches such as saws, tree wrapping, and even candy-cane painted tools. Guests can enjoy the festive outdoor setting, warm up by the fire, and take home a beautiful fresh-cut tree to make their holiday season complete.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blitzen Estate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/blitzen-estate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/blitzen-estate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Blitzen Estate is a Christmas tree, maple syrup, and horse farm located in Jasper, Ontario, created by Caylyn and Kevin after leaving behind their fast-paced corporate careers. With backgrounds in health and safety management and corporate sales, the couple traded in global travel and high-stakes deals for small-town living and a farm that celebrates nature, tradition, and seasonal joy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;At Blitzen Estate, visitors will find more than just Christmas trees and maple syrup. Caylyn’s passion for horses brings unique experiences to the farm, with plans for sleigh rides, haunted hay rides, and other seasonal events that capture the festive spirit. Meanwhile, Kevin’s love for country living, combined with his people skills and storytelling, creates a warm and welcoming atmosphere for guests year-round.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blue Harvest Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/blue-harvest-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/blue-harvest-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Blue Harvest Farm is more than a Christmas tree farm—it’s a place built to feel like home. Originally the family homestead, it is now run by the owner, her husband David, their children Blake and Samira, and their red retriever Elaina. Surrounded by beautiful views and breathtaking sunsets, the farm invites guests to experience the joy of choosing the perfect Christmas tree while creating lasting family memories.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Giving back has always been at the heart of Blue Harvest Farm. For many years, the family hosted an annual sale of one-of-a-kind garden trial plants to support local charities and their hospital. Today, that tradition of generosity continues with the Giving Tree Ornaments, where 100% of sales go directly toward helping local families enjoy a memorable Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boat Harbour Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/boat-harbour-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/boat-harbour-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Boat Harbour Farm is a 5-acre Christmas tree farm located in Cedar, BC, just south of Nanaimo. It offers a &amp;lsquo;you pick, we cut, we shake, you load&amp;rsquo; experience, allowing customers to choose their tree while it&amp;rsquo;s still standing in the field. The farm grows a variety of tree types including Douglas Fir, Grand Fir, Noble Fir, Nordmann Fir, Concolor Fir, Colorado Spruce, and Canaan Fir. Customers can park in the lower field and take their time selecting the perfect tree. After the tree is cut, it is shaken to remove loose needles, bird nests, and other debris. Pets are welcome but must be kept on a leash. The farm accepts cash, credit, and debit payments. It will be closed until the 2025 Christmas season.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Boisé Brabant</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/bois-brabant/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/bois-brabant/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To enjoy the experience of cutting your own Christmas tree at Boisé Brabant, visitors are asked to book a date in advance at 721 Martel Rd. This system helps manage demand, reduce crowding, and ensure a safe, enjoyable visit for everyone, while also protecting the long-term sustainability of the tree plantation. Please note that the season is shorter this year, and trees will only be available while supplies last.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Boisé Brabant was founded in 2002 when Sylvie and Yvon embraced the chance to build something new as retirement approached. What began as a small Christmas tree venture has blossomed into both a family tradition and a local destination, where three generations now work together to welcome visitors each holiday season.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Briggs Trees</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/briggs-trees/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/briggs-trees/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Briggs Tree Farm is a family-owned and operated farm that has been growing and selling Christmas trees to the Ottawa community for over 40 years. Nestled within a beautiful 100-acre woodland, the farm offers a traditional and memorable holiday experience where visitors can stroll through the forest to find their perfect tree.&#xA;The farm features a variety of trees ideal for Christmas, including Scotch Pine, Balsam Fir, White Spruce, and Norway Spruce. Each tree is carefully trimmed to maintain a natural shape, with a range of sizes and fullness to suit every home and holiday style.&#xA;Visitors are invited to enjoy a walk through the scenic woods, cut their own spruce, balsam, or scotch pine tree, and select a handcrafted natural Christmas wreath—making Briggs Tree Farm a festive destination for families year after year.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calgary Christmas Tree</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/calgary-christmas-tree/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/calgary-christmas-tree/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Description coming soon&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carole&#39;s Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/caroles-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/caroles-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Carole’s Christmas Tree Farm has been family-owned and operated for more than 25 years, continuing a cherished tradition of offering a natural and memorable Christmas tree experience. Now in its ninth season under the current generation, the farm was built on the idea of recreating the timeless tradition of families strolling through forests in search of the perfect Christmas tree.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2023, Carole’s Christmas Tree Farm made the difficult decision to suspend its cut-your-own service. This change allows the farm to rehabilitate, while also addressing liability concerns and the increase in vandalism experienced during the 2022 season.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Carr Family Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/carr-family-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/carr-family-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Description coming soon&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Catfish Creek Christmas Tree Farm</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/farms/catfish-creek-christmas-tree-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/farms/catfish-creek-christmas-tree-farm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Catfish Creek Christmas Tree Farm has a rich history rooted in family tradition. The land was first purchased in 1974 by Gordon’s parents, where Gordon spent his childhood helping with farm life—selling eggs, raising chickens, and caring for horses.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2002, Gordon purchased the farm from his parents and began shaping it with his own vision. By 2009, alongside his wife Corinne, the couple planted and began maintaining 500 Christmas tree seedlings, laying the foundation for what would become a cherished holiday destination.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
